If you dig too deep, you may not like what comes up
Backstabbing for Beginners is a thriller, drama,
history film directed by Per Fly.
An idealistic young employee at the U.N.
investigates the grisly murder of his predecessor – and uncovers a
vast global conspiracy that may involve his own boss.
Michael, played by Theo James.
Christina Dupre, played by Jacqueline Bisset.
Pasha, played by Ben Kingsley.
Trevor, played by Rossif Sutherland.
Rasnetsov, played by Brian Markinson.
Lily, played by Rachel Wilson.
Backstabbing for Beginners is a 2018 political thriller film directed and
co-written by Per Fly, and based on the memoirs of Michael Soussan.
It follows the real life corruption scandal in the UN Oil-for-Food
Programme, and stars Theo James and Ben Kingsley.
The tone is emotional and intense.